<contentList>
	<content contentuid="h16e000a2g7acbg4f28g93fagcfb26f8676cb" Source="Odinblade Pyro"                >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Phoenix, a flexible support focused on simultaneously buffing allies and debuffing enemies.</content>
	<content contentuid="hac6b87a9g8ab5g481bg9595g6d9a3d4dc9d6" Source="Odinblade Pyro"                >*Say you&apos;re looking for an Arsonist, a pyromaniac hell-bent on setting the battlefield ablaze.</content>
	<content contentuid="h84b36689gde88g4c80ga694g1944ca4ca8dc" Source="Odinblade Pyro"                >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Scorcher, a gifted fire mage specialising in devastating damage-over-time effects.</content>
	<content contentuid="h73b8b8bagb588g492agbc09g26e891be4db8" Source="Odinblade Pyro"                >*Say you&apos;re looking for an Infernal, a bulky hybrid damager with a penchant for pyrokinesis.</content>
	<content contentuid="h93166abfga66cg424dg8452ge5a3e80469c0" Source="Odinblade Necro"               >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Deathlord, a warrior beyond death who feasts on the life force of others.</content>
	<content contentuid="h0a0aad5egc90fg4f07gb63bg7820bf0bb65e" Source="Odinblade Necro"               >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Bloodtide, a master of sanguimancy who sacrifices vitality to inflict pain onto others.</content>
	<content contentuid="h84443eceg0b11g4e1fg9b4ag8eb510d75d1b" Source="Odinblade Necro"               >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Hexen, a witch armed with a plethora of powerful buffs and debuffs.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd9ea54b9gd537g4d00g9ec2gb8786eb3751f" Source="Odinblade Necro"               >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Gravecaller, a necromancer able to raise the undead to do their bidding.</content>
	<content contentuid="ha6020ce3g00f0g4994gaca5g67fedd1270fb" Source="Odinblade Geo"                 >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Terramancer, a stone mage able to manipulate the fabric of the earth.</content>
	<content contentuid="h09fea150g7abdg4779gae96g0c0945ec13a6" Source="Odinblade Geo"                 >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Sentinel, an impenetrable warrior who is tough as steel.</content>
	<content contentuid="h6b73a0e0g5b1fg4d0bg8dfbga38145189ce1" Source="Odinblade Geo"                 >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Grovetender, a preserver of nature who nourishes allies by commanding plant life.</content>
	<content contentuid="h5fe34f70g8931g475eg8fb0g5c6e4432d909" Source="Odinblade Geo"                 >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Plague, a wickedly-cruel poison mage excelling in deadly concoctions.</content>
	<content contentuid="h0124ed97g1406g44a1ga5cfg2794c0f7b8e5" Source="Odinblade Aero"                >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Windweaver, a maestro of the winds who keeps their foes afar.</content>
	<content contentuid="h73a7d298g2d48g4de0ga2d3g764957389f10" Source="Odinblade Aero"                >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Thunderlord, a warrior blessed with a lightning-charged hammer.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf4ed0617g0c89g4d6cg97b8g6af39b704848" Source="Odinblade Aero"                >*Say you&apos;re looking for an Electromancer, a maniacal mage able to fork electricity across the battlefield.</content>
	<content contentuid="hff5bd9a4g40f9g40bfga2f4g8debaff0eeb0" Source="Odinblade Aero"                >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Tempest, a mage able to manipulate the atmosphere to conjure storms and cloud-based surfaces.</content>
	<content contentuid="ha3b0d635g56a2g49abg9c18gedb1b93cc0d9" Source="Odinblade Hydro"               >*Say you&apos;re looking for an Icevein, a cryomancer who keeps their foes frozen in place.</content>
	<content contentuid="h8026e0a1gcb3ag4087ga962g0d4c5ad2807d" Source="Odinblade Hydro"               >*Say you&apos;re looking for an Atlantean, a deep sea warrior armed with a water-infused trident.</content>
	<content contentuid="h948b0dcfg65ddg450fg8ef2g738365a71190" Source="Odinblade Hydro"               >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Tidecaller, a hydro mage gifted with the ability to manipulate the seas.</content>
	<content contentuid="hb186642egbc97g48ddgaf8agc52f8d542e6d" Source="Odinblade Hydro"               >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Frostsworn, a frost paladin specialising in Magic Armour effects.</content>
	<content contentuid="hcd1c6f9cg8908g4eb0g9d63g3069d1c55b96" Source="Odinblade Umbra"               >*Say you&apos;re looking for an Umbra, an assassin who switches between damage types to kill their mark.</content>
	<content contentuid="h9c1ca86egff71g4742g92begd6a58c87bb11" Source="Odinblade Spectre"             >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Spectre, a practioner of forbidden soul magic who blurs the line between life and death.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc95e0290ge252g470eg8f46g0b1296e86886" Source="Odinblade Huntsman"            >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Tracker, an expert hunter with a trusty Animal Companion by their side.</content>
	<content contentuid="hfe6e3615g90a2g490dg8560g07683a10563e" Source="Odinblade Scoundrel"           >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Nightcloak, an assassin who dips in and out of visibility to unleash a flurry of deadly strikes.</content>
	<content contentuid="h900c1cb0g522bg47bfgb899gb1b473d76f4e" Source="Heaphaistos Constellationist"  >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Constellationist, a wizard that borrows their power from the celestial world to wield as they see fit.</content>
	<content contentuid="h25309aa3g4642g4fb4gb1bag38ff3712f8a6" Source="Heaphaistos Astronomer"        >*Say you&apos;re looking for an Astronomer, a wizard who manipulates aspects of the sun and moon to buff and debuff whoever they desire.</content>
	<content contentuid="h25651c93g1513g4466g8d3dg8c84ee8e0e71" Source="Heaphaistos Beserker"          >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Beserker, an insane warrior motivated by their unquenchable fury and strength in battle.</content>
	<content contentuid="h8d3c1078g223cg428aga6d0g88012ccfb81a" Source="Heaphaistos Chronomancer"      >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Chronomancer, an extraordinary mage with limited control over time and space itself.</content>
	<content contentuid="hbd22c782g7b3fg48b1gbca7g896ba1c351f2" Source="Helaene Trickster"             >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Trickster, someone adept at making mischief and magic wherever they turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="h83295ec7g8ea7g4c48g915dg0c166c469c8e" Source="Helaene Valkyrie"              >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Valkyrie, a true warrior and feared chooser of the slain.</content>
	<content contentuid="h9a9706b2ge6d0g4b1dg9d7agafd06183bda8" Source="Helaene Mirage"                >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Mirage, a mage channeling chaos and illusion under the desert sun.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd20a6733g1133g4e69g98afg759c9d167450" Source="Helaene Blacksmith"            >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Blacksmith, a warrior who can smash enemies with a hammer and repair your gear all the same.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1c2a9c25g8ddbg438aga7d2g77b2910d11f3" Source="Helaene Wyldfae"               >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Wyldfae, a mage in harmony with Mother Nature and dominion over flora and fauna.</content>
	<content contentuid="h92be7db9gf05dg4661gafbcg0321f71dc541" Source="Helaene Succubus"              >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Succubus, a demon well versed in the timeless arts of romance and seduction.</content>
	<content contentuid="h3d0247ecgc26fg4601gb0f0g584546e7b8e1" Source="Helaene Vampire"               >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Vampire, a terrifying warrior that draws power and sustenance from the blood of their enemies.</content>
	<content contentuid="hecde40a4ga4b9g47dfg9fd5g45e0df8c8b01" Source="Helaene Cryomancer"            >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Cryomancer, a mage adept at strengthening themself with ice and freezing enemies.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf69853f1g6577g484bg8af1ge3ca5566aad2" Source="Helaene Priest"                >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Priest, a true support executing the will of the Divine.</content>
	<content contentuid="haeb53dafgd386g42a4g9b00gdbef71359807" Source="Feenex Battle Pack"            >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Monk, an unarmed warrior that supports allies and brings down wrath on foes.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1eb479ddg2b02g4b5fg8c2cg0444ad60ebbc" Source="Feenex Battle Pack"            >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Paladin, a warrior of retribution capable of defending allies and dealing justice.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd306e3eag194dg4f4fga3b8g95b72c7c0ac7" Source="Feenex Battle Pack"            >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Deathknight, a warrior of darkness who can inflict great curses to enemies.</content>
	<content contentuid="h36b10b39g5533g489dg9c3bg2226f2753b9c" Source="Feenex Battle Pack"            >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Druid, a supportive mage whose healing is only outmatched by their versatility.</content>
	<content contentuid="h504a88ebg3086g4a59g8089ga7a80f54be13" Source="Feenex Battle Pack"            >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Shaman, a wicked witch that excels at debilitating their opponents.</content>
	<content contentuid="h4519c5bcg3279g45f2ga3cege6bb2cf43bf4" Source="Feenex Battle Pack"            >*Say you&apos;re looking for an Arcanist, a mage capable of controlling the battlefield with flashy magic.</content>
	<content contentuid="h17ac77c4g2244g429aga195g0abb420e2950" Source="Feenex Battle Pack"            >*Say you&apos;re looking for an Eldritch Knight, a warrior that conjours magical weapons and wields magic to strike down their foes.</content>
	<content contentuid="h4dc55e88g3982g49d2gb46eg0ee32bb6ae88" Source="Feenex Battle Pack"            >*Say you&apos;re looking for an Arcane Archer, someone with the ability to conjure a magical bow and shoot mystical arrows.</content>
	<content contentuid="h5d1bcf89ge120g48acga782gaab52860a010" Source="Feenex Expanded"               >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Shade, a dark wizard that manipulates the shadows into horrible forms to torment their enemies.</content>
	<content contentuid="h5835425ag0b28g4439gae3cgb8a841e1fa38" Source="Feenex Expanded"               >*Say you&apos;re looking for an Elementist, an elemental wizard with astounding versatility.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd781508ag8cedg4893g95d1ga213c22e6114" Source="Feenex Expanded"               >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Totemancer, an elemental caster who specialises in summoning totems to strike foes.</content>
	<content contentuid="ha1239879gdaaeg472dg8fc0gb2eac7b25d24" Source="Feenex Expanded"               >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Barbarian, a primal warrior that utilises their fury to full effect.</content>
	<content contentuid="h8eded1fbg42afg4d02g98a1g5377b21337ea" Source="Feenex Expanded"               >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Shadowmancer, a dark wizard that unleashes the terrors of the shadows onto their victims.</content>
	<content contentuid="h9a5cf4bfg6079g428dga6a9g542e9bb4b4b9" Source="Feenex Shapeshifting"          >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Shapeshifter, a warrior and master of transformation into many powerful forms.</content>
	<content contentuid="h0ed31e1fgd4e5g4dd7ga355g7bd546197fa6" Source="Feenex Shapeshifting"          >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Beastspeaker, a mage capable of both summoning and transforming others into powerful beasts.</content>
	<content contentuid="h31314c5bg9fc1g4fe6ga488g3abd3f676e05" Source="LaughingLeader Mimicry"        >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Mime, a warrior that can mimic the actions of allies in battle.</content>
	<content contentuid="h820e6dbdga817g4c4cg9a16gf1dea5197c81" Source="Auracheetah Scourge"           >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Scourge, a maniacal wizard capable of spreading plague throughout the battlefied.</content>
	<content contentuid="h93df3a7dgc9e7g4138gac69ga1322ba831fa" Source="SirGagz Venalguard"            >*Say you&apos;re looking for a Venalguard, a cursed warrior capable of wielding two blades along with destructive jade magic.</content>
</contentList>